https://www.medicare.gov/forms-help-resources/help-fight-medicare-fraud

Main Menu
Don’t wait: Medicare Advantage Open Enrollment ends March 31Privacy policyWhat’s a home health care plan?Sign Up
/
Change PlansGet started with MedicareHow do I get Parts A & B?I have employer coverageApply for Medicare onlineWhen can I join a health or drug plan?Types of Medicare health plansFind health & drug plansCheck your enrollmentAbout UsYour Medicare CostsGet help paying costsPart A costsPart B costsCosts for Medicare health plansCompare procedure costsWays to pay Part A & Part B premiumsCosts at a glanceWhat Medicare CoversIs my test, item, or service covered?Your Medicare coverage choicesWhat Part A coversWhat Part B coversWhat Medicare health plans coverPreventive & screening servicesWhat's not covered by Part A & Part BDrug Coverage (Part D)How to get prescription drug coverageWhat Medicare Part D drug plans coverCosts for Medicare drug coverageHow Part D works with other insuranceSupplements & Other InsuranceHow Medicare works with other insuranceRetiree insuranceWhat's Medicare Supplement Insurance (Medigap)?Find a Medigap policyWhen can I buy Medigap?How to compare Medigap policiesMedigap & travelClaims & AppealsFile a complaint (grievance)File a claimCheck the status of a claimFile an appealYour right to a fast appealYour Medicare rightsAuthorization to Disclose Personal Health InformationManage Your HealthLogin to MyMedicare.gov Advance directives & long-term careElectronic prescribingMedicare's Blue Button & Blue Button 2.0Coordinating your careInformation for my situationI have a disabilityI have End-Stage Renal Disease (ESRD)Forms, Help, & ResourcesFind careMedicare formsFree Medicare publications"Medicare & You" handbookMail you get about MedicareLost/incorrect Medicare cardReport fraud & abuseIdentity theft: protect yourselfPhone numbers & websitesPrivacy practicesContact Medicare
Main Menu
Show — Main Menu
Hide — Main Menu
Don’t wait: Medicare Advantage Open Enrollment ends March 31
Privacy policy
What’s a home health care plan?
Sign Up
/
Change Plans
Get started with Medicare
How do I get Parts A & B?
I have employer coverage
Apply for Medicare online
When can I join a health or drug plan?
Types of Medicare health plans
Find health & drug plans
Check your enrollment
About Us
Your Medicare Costs
Get help paying costs
Part A costs
Part B costs
Costs for Medicare health plans
Compare procedure costs
Ways to pay Part A & Part B premiums
Costs at a glance
What Medicare Covers
Is my test, item, or service covered?
Your Medicare coverage choices
What Part A covers
What Part B covers
What Medicare health plans cover
Preventive & screening services
What's not covered by Part A & Part B
Drug Coverage (Part D)
How to get prescription drug coverage
What Medicare Part D drug plans cover
Costs for Medicare drug coverage
How Part D works with other insurance
Supplements & Other Insurance
How Medicare works with other insurance
Retiree insurance
What's Medicare Supplement Insurance (Medigap)?
Find a Medigap policy
When can I buy Medigap?
How to compare Medigap policies
Medigap & travel
Claims & Appeals
File a complaint (grievance)
File a claim
Check the status of a claim
File an appeal
Your right to a fast appeal
Your Medicare rights
Authorization to Disclose Personal Health Information
Manage Your Health
Login to MyMedicare.gov
Advance directives & long-term care
Electronic prescribing
Medicare's Blue Button & Blue Button 2.0
Coordinating your care
Information for my situation
I have a disability
I have End-Stage Renal Disease (ESRD)
Forms, Help, & Resources
Find care
Medicare forms
Free Medicare publications
"Medicare & You" handbook
Mail you get about Medicare
Lost/incorrect Medicare card
Report fraud & abuse
Note
Stay alert for fraud during the coronavirus national emergency. Con artists like to take advantage of people when they’re distracted.
Con artists may try to get your Medicare Number or personal information so they can steal your identity and commit Medicare fraud. Medicare fraud results in higher health care costs and taxes for everyone.
Protect yourself from Medicare fraud. Guard your Medicare card like it’s a credit card. Remember:
Medicare will never contact you for your Medicare Number or other personal information unless you’ve given them permission in advance.
Medicare will never call you to sell you anything.
You may get calls from people promising you things if you give them a Medicare Number. Don’t do it.
Medicare will never visit you at your home.
Medicare can’t enroll you over the phone unless you called first.
Learn more tips to help prevent Medicare fraud.
Check regularly for Medicare billing fraud. Review your Medicare claims and Medicare Summary Notices for any services billed to your Medicare Number you don’t recognize.
Learn more about how to spot fraud.
Report anything suspicious to Medicare. If you suspect fraud, call 1-800-MEDICARE.
Learn how to report fraud.
Related Resources
Medicare fraud: Don’t give them a chance
Medicare & You: Preventing Medicare Fraud
Medicare Fraud Strike Force
Find someone to talk to
Find someone to talk to in your state Select your state...AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasU.S. Minor Outlying IslandsUtahVermontVirgin Islands of the U.S.VirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Is my test, item, or service covered?
Go
Footer
Home
A federal government website managed and paid for by the U.S. Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services.
Main navigation
Show — Main navigation
Hide — Main navigation
Don’t wait: Medicare Advantage Open Enrollment ends March 31
Privacy policy
What’s a home health care plan?
Sign Up
/
Change Plans
About Us
Your Medicare Costs
What Medicare Covers
Drug Coverage (Part D)
Supplements & Other Insurance
Claims & Appeals
Manage Your Health
Forms, Help, & Resources
Take Action
Show — Take Action
Hide — Take Action
Find health & drug plans
Find care
Where can I get covered medical items?
Get Medicare forms
Publications
Information in other languages
Phone numbers & websites
Helpful Links
Show — Helpful Links
Hide — Helpful Links
Site Map
Your Privacy Options
We take your privacy seriously. You can change the settings below to make sure you're comfortable with the ways we collect and use information while you're on Medicare.gov. For more information, please see our privacy notice.
Category
Description
Status
Advertising
We use digital advertising tools, such as web beacons, to track the effectiveness of our digital advertising outreach efforts. This helps us identify ads that are helpful to consumers and efficient for outreach. Selecting OFF will block this tracking.
On
Off
Social Media
If you share our content on Facebook, Twitter, or other social media accounts, we may track what Medicare.gov content you share. This helps us improve our social media outreach. Selecting OFF will block this tracking.
On
Off
Web Analytics
We use a variety of tools to count, track, and analyze visits to Medicare.gov. This helps us understand how people use the site and where we should make improvements. Selecting OFF will block this tracking.
On
Off
